we7.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy policy

## 1\. Our Commitment to You

Welcome to we7, the next generation music service where users can get the digital entertainment they want free, legally, safely and share between friends, family and other users. we7 are passionate about music and respect artists and their craft. The founders and employees of we7 take your privacy very seriously. To make it easier for you to read and understand our privacy policy, we have written it in plain English and a reasonably short length.

  * Your privacy remains strictly under your control 
  * You can end your membership at any time 
  * we7 does not spam 

## 2\. Information Collected by we7

When you register to become a user of we7, you submit information such as your name, year of birth, gender, postcode/zipcode and email address. Over time you may provide or we will ask you to provide additional information which will extend your personal profile so we can increase our ability to ensure relevance of any messaging, you may choose to provide additional information to help this process.

We also collect other non-personally identifiable data, which may include your IP address and what browser you are using.

## 3\. Use of Information

We will display your personal information on your profile according to the preferences you set in your account. We will use your name so that we can personalise your experience. We will use your email address to contact you from time to time and we will use your email address for security reasons to confirm that you are who you say you are. You can control the types and frequencies of certain emails you receive.

In the event that you do not want we7 to use your email address to contact you from time to time kindly send an email from your membership/user address headed "NO MORE we7 MARKETING EMAILS" to [info@we7.com](mailto:info@we7.com?subject=NO%20MORE%20we7%20MARKETING%20EMAILS).

We may use the non-personally identifiable information, like your IP address, to statistically analyse site usage and to customise our site's content, layout and services. The resulting information will allow us to improve our site and better understand and serve our users.

To enable delivery of free, safe, legal music we will use the non-personally identifiable information to decide what ad/message to include with chosen tracks to download or stream.

We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect the rights and property of we7, its affiliates or the public. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency in doing so.

## 4\. You Control Who Shares Your Information

With the exception of "Bands" who chose to have details in the public domain we will not share your identifiable personal data with other users unless you specifically choose to do so.

At a future time it is intended that you can choose to make your profile visible to users of we7 by editing your profile and opting in to "accessible profile".

One of our goals is to enrich the Band-Fan relationship as well as building relationships with other communities and other music related business. We reserve the right to share information between any such relationships, which may or may not involve financial payment between we7 and other parties. 

## 5\. Reviewing and Changing Your Profile

You can review and revise your personal profile at any time.

## 6\. Internet Awareness

Whenever you voluntarily post personal information in public areas, like journals, weblogs, reviews, message boards, and forums, you should be aware that this information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by others to send you unsolicited communications. Please exercise discretion in deciding what information you disclose.

## 7\. Minors

Our policy is to request that "Minors" (the age of Minors is determined by local law where you reside) do not make purchases or engage in other legal acts on this site without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless permitted by applicable local law.

## 8\. Effective Date

This Privacy Policy statement is effective as of [9th June 2008].

## 9\. Use of Cookies

Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so.

## 10\. Third Party Advertising

we7 may share profile information in a personally identifiable manner and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties in order to present to users more targeted advertising, products and services. Advertisements that appear on this web site and added to digital downloads are delivered to users by ourselves and our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may set cookies.

## 11\. Business Transition

In the event that we7 goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sells a portion of its assets, users' information, in most instances, is a part of the assets transferred. Such a transfer will not be considered a violation of or deviation from this policy.

## 12\. Security

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorised people. we7 uses industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us.

## 13\. International Server Locations

By using the we7 site you accept and give your consent that data obtained in connection with your use of this site may be transferred, if permitted by applicable local legislation across international borders to server locations supporting the we7 website for operating and developing the we7 website and services.

## 14\. Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of this website or our service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

## 15\. Cancelling Membership

You always have the option to cancel your membership at any time. If you wish to cancel your membership please email us.

## 16\. Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via the contact us page, or by writing to:

Support Department  
we7 Ltd  
Manches Building,  
9400 Garsington Road,  
Oxford Business Park,  
Oxford,  
OX4 2HN.
